GUYS.
>> CARLOS THANK YOU LA COUNTY
HAS DECLARED A STATE OF
EMERGENCY FOLLOWING RECENT
IMMIGRATION RAIDS IN OFFERS
EXPANDED FINANCIAL AID TO
RENTERS WHO ARE STRUGGLING
FINANCIALLY DUE TO IMMIGRATION
ARREST LANDLORDS AND APARTMENT
OWNERS ASSOCIATIONS. POSE
KTLA. JEAN KING IN THE
NEWSROOM NOW WITH THE LATEST
ON THAT FOR US JEANNE GOOD
MORNING, GOOD MORNING, JUSTIN
FRANK LA COUNTY DECLARED A
STATE OF EMERGENCY DUE TO
FEDERAL IMMIGRATION RAIDS.
>> THE BOARD OF SUPERVISORS
VOTED TO TAKE ACTION HELPING
FAMILIES WHO HAVE FACED MAJOR
FAMILIES WHO HAVE FACED MAOJR
VOTED TO TAKE ACTION HELPING
FAMILIES WHO HAVE FACED MAJOR
FINANCIAL BURDENS LA COUNTY IS
OFFICIALLY IN A LOCAL
EMERGENCY OVER FEDERAL ICE
RAIDS THAT HAVE BEEN TAKING
PLACE SINCE SUMMER. THE BOARD
OF SUPERVISORS IS MOVING
FORWARD THIS MORNING. THEY
VOTED 4 TO ONE YESTERDAY
SAYING THE RAIDS PUT THOUSANDS
OF FAMILIES IN FINANCIAL
DANGER. THE DECLARATION LETS
THE COUNTY TAKE ADVANTAGE OF
STATE MONEY AND OUTSIDE
RESOURCES FOR COUNTY RELIEF
LEGAL AID AND EVEN BUYING
FOOD.
>> FOR MONTHS FAMILIES HAVE
BEEN LIVING UNDER THREAT.
WORKERS HAVE BEEN KIDNAPPED
FROM JOB SITES. AND CHILDREN
HAVE BEEN COMING HOME TO EMPTY
DINNER TABLES. LOS ANGELES
COUNTY HAS A RESPONSIBILITY TO
PROTECT EVERY RESIDENT. NO
MATTER WHERE THEY COME FROM OR
WHAT PAPERS THEY CARRY.
DECLARING A LOCAL EMERGENCY
ALLOWS US TO MOVE FASTER TO
MEET THAT RESPONSIBILITY.
>> AND FOR THOSE WHO WANT TO
APPLY AN ONLINE PORTAL FOR
RENT HELP SHOULD TAKE OFF IN A
COUPLE OF MONTHS. BUT SOME
LANDLORDS THIS MORNING ARE
WORRIED THAT THIS COULD LEAD
TO ANOTHER EVICTION MORATORIUM
LIKE THE ONE WE HAD DURING THE
PANDEMIC SUPERVISOR KATHRYN
BARGER WAS THE ONLY NO VOTE
QUESTIONING IF THIS EMERGENCY
DECLARATION REALLY CHANGES
ANYTHING OR IF IT JUST INVITES
LEGAL CHALLENGES FROM THE
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION. DURING
OPEN COMMENT. THERE WAS A MIX
OF OPINIONS FROM RESIDENTS.
>> EMERGENCY DECLARATIONS ONLY
NEEDED TO PASS ANOTHER COUNTY
WAY TO FIX MORATORIUM, 3RD
EVICTION MARTIN WILL BE THE
DEATH BLOW TO MANY MOM AND POP
ON A STRUGGLING FROM YEARS OF
UNPAID RENT FROM THE PANDEMIC
IN THE WILDFIRES.
>> JUST LAST NIGHT ON FOX NEWS
SEAN HANNITY HAD US ATTORNEY
PAM BONDI ON HIS SHOW AND THEY
TALKED ABOUT LA COUNTY STATE
OF EMERGENCY, NOT HOLDING
BACK. IN LA THEY DECLARE STATE
OF EMERGENCY AND. TO AID
RESIDENTS HIT BY IMMIGRATION
RATES. HOW A TERM ADAM
ATTORNEY GENERAL HOW IS THAT
NOT AIDING AND ABETTING IN LAW
BREAK. IT IS SEAN. IT IS.